<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>evanrose.com</title>
<link>http://evanrose.com</link>
<description>evanrose.com syndicated</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 14:20:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>Giving the Site a Haircut</title>
<description>Recently I refactored almost all of the code that powers the backend of this site, a lot of which has been around for however long it's been since I built the content management system that powers it (and perhaps before - I had another blog that I ran on my Mac out of my apartment when I lived in Oakland whose code made its way into this site). Tired of being the cobbler whose kids have no shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, permalinks. They have always been something like evanrose.com/?entry=100 which I thought was cool back in the day (hey, I know PHP!) but long past their sell by date. I built a system that turns the blog post's title into a slug and am using those for permalinks (and being a good web citizen, should someone come into the site via a link to a post with an entry id, they will get seamlessly redirected). Secondly, I changed an .htaccess redirect that would, for example, redirect evanrose.com/work to evanrose.com/?section=work. This has been changed so that all requests end up on index.php and the non-query-stringed URL is split and used. Even the HTML templates I used before I entered blog posts in to a database work with this new scheme (for the most part, at least they're used in the virtual blog directory) for instance, my first month of blogging on evanrose.com (and not on my previous sites) in &lt;a href=&quot;http://evanrose.com/blog/?date=0107&quot;&gt;July of 2001&lt;/a&gt;  and without touching that templated file, it validates as HTML 5!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, back in the day, I didn't know about how to deal with dates and math and whatnot coming from a database so my noob self saved date oriented data like so: insert &quot;Tuesday&quot; into `day name`, etc., which is just NASTY. I was young and I needed the money. Fixed all that garbage (and should have years ago). I also fixed a bunch of hacky crap to deal with page titles and whatnot which was also trivial. It was pleasant work cleaning this business up and by god it might last me another ten years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please don't make me be blogging in ten years. </description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=612</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=612#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 14:20:32 -0800</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=612</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hell of Links</title>
<description>Hell of links for Gunnar from Kottke:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kottke.org/13/08/the-surprising-ages-of-the-founding-fathers-on-july-4-1776&quot;&gt;The surprising ages of the Founding Fathers on July 4, 1776&lt;/a&gt; if only for the story of a bad ass at the end, via @kottke&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kottke.org/13/08/july-1852-nyc&quot;&gt;July 1852 NYC&lt;/a&gt; via @kottke again, though possibly written by &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Achewood&quot;&gt;Chris Onstad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kottke.org/13/08/the-suits-of-james-bond&quot;&gt;The Suits of James Bond&lt;/a&gt; which is obviously written by a tailor or some other very sartorially inclined person and is fantastic (via @kottke)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just hell of links.</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=611</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=611#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 14:00:15 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=611</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sailing in the Keys</title>
<description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/sets/72157634795520567/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://farm4.staticflickr.com/3670/9370711444_ebab91f76f_t.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Last month, I spent a week on a sailboat, bopping around from Florida Key to Florid Key and bopping around in Key West.  I had no idea how much fun this would be, though a week was probably a couple of days too long.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/sets/72157634795520567/&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;&gt;I took a bunch of photos&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/evanrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Youtube&quot;&gt;shot some really cool video&lt;/a&gt;.  Check 'em out.  </description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=610</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=610#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 06:50:58 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=610</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>On Work</title>
<description>First, Louis CK on work (and of course, being awesome)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/dKT9v3PwmvA&quot; seamless=&quot;seamless&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And recently, a note to self on work:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Treat it like it's the most important thing in the world because it is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be nice.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smile! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't use your phone. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not a single personal social web site [ed: not really doing much of this anyway, but still]. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work.  Hard.  This is your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;!-- 

Remember how hard Erica worked and how impressed you were by that.  How proud and respectful of her you were.  She was indispensable. 

And please help Erica to be happy, healthy, and prosperous.

--&gt;

&lt;li&gt;They like you.  They wanted you.  They're paying you, but they will stop if you don't do a good job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't forget how painful and humiliating the interview process was.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't forget about &lt;!-- ERICA'S--&gt; the loss of respect&lt;!-- FOR YOU --&gt;.*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don't leave the office; they are paying attentiion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You make &lt;!-- $75 --&gt; X per hour.  That is a ton of money.  Earn as much as you can every day.  9 to six, no matter how painful &lt;b&gt;that&lt;/b&gt; is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This project will be harder than you think it will be, but it can be done.  Don't get cocky, but don't get mad.  Do the work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, read this every single day.</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=609</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=609#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 04:48:16 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=609</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>Texas, Then and Now</title>
<description>Went to Dallas and Austin recently (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/sets/72157631911728805/&quot;&gt;here are the pics&lt;/a&gt;) for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bigtex.com/sft/&quot;&gt;State Fair of Texas&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dallasnews.com/entertainment/state-fair-of-texas/headlines/20121019-state-fair-of-texas-icon-big-tex-goes-up-in-flames.ece&quot;&gt;RIP, Big Tex&lt;/a&gt;) and to take part in the nuptuals of &lt;a href=&quot;http://atechnologyjobisnoexcuse.com/&quot;&gt;Gunnar&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://swedish-hawaiian-friendship-society.org/about-ingrid-and-gunnar/&quot;&gt;Ingrid&lt;/a&gt;, two of the finest people a man would want to know.  Much fun was had and much fried food was consumed.  At the fair alone:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 fried frito pie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 fried okra&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 frito pie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 fried okra&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 fried max cheese slider&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 fried okra&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 corny dog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/8148535908/in/set-72157631911728805&quot;&gt;corny dog&lt;/a&gt;.&quot;  In addition, there was lots of driving, lots of meals with my mom, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dallasarboretum.org/chihuly/&quot;&gt;Dale Chihuly show at the Dallas Arboretum&lt;/a&gt;, lots of catching up with old and making new friends and hell of fun in general.  Though it was fun, I got stuck there while Sandy descended upon New York and couldn't wait to get home, which is exactly why I'm going back to Texas again tomorrow.  See you Texas peops soon.  </description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=608</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=608#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 14:03:53 -0800</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=608</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>Recently, On My Corner of the Web...</title>
<description>Did some more cleaning up around here.  Even though those sites have moved on to greener pastures, I've put up links to some of my older freelance work that lives on my own server, &lt;a href=&quot;http://beertable2.com.s14910.gridserver.com/&quot;&gt;Beer Table version 1&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://beertable2.com.s14910.gridserver.com/&quot;&gt;Beer Table version 2&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://btpantry.com.s14910.gridserver.com/&quot;&gt;Beer Table Pantry&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://nickistager.com.s14910.gridserver.com/&quot;&gt;Nikki Stager&lt;/a&gt;, the last being one, I really like but which never got used, though the images getting pulled in from &lt;a href=&quot;http://flickr.com/photos/evanrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt; can be a little flaky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, my first project for &lt;a href=&quot;http://people.com&quot;&gt;people.com&lt;/a&gt; is now live: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.people.com/people/static/h/readerreact/&quot;&gt;Reader React&lt;/a&gt;.  I built this almost from scratch, using only the container and a forked copy of their javascript commenting system.  First, PHP fetches a JSON feed of all of the articles that have had the highest comment counts for the past 24 hours.  Next, each article gets a container and its data is put into it (though in the case of data from People's Wordpress blog, another JSON feed is fetched, parsed and inserted).  Following that, each article id is put into an array which builds an url which is fetched by JQuery and parsed so that each article gets its comment counts as well as the commenting module for that article itself (which required the fork of their commenting system - this need was not foreseen).  Finally, valid XHTML and CSS style the results, which have get written to disk as HTML by a cron job that runs every ten minutes.  Fun project.  Keep 'em coming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/evanallenrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Instagram&quot;&gt;Instagram added profiles and here is mine&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=607</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=607#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 13:58:02 -0800</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=607</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>Katherine, Jim, and Steve</title>
<description>Today, I'm off for a long weekend of dinner, &lt;a href=&quot;http://barnforeachother.com&quot;&gt;the nuptials of my friends Katherine and Jim&lt;/a&gt;, Katherine being one of the first friends I made when I moved to New York eight and a half years ago and Jim being one of the greatest dudes I've ever met, and a brunch in Connecticut and Massachusetts.  I'm almost positive much fun will be had.  Today also marks the date of a sad day a year ago, and I'll let my journal entry from that day speak for itself:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;October 5, 2011&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&quot;My mom wrote me an email talking about what she wanted to have happen if she suffered from dementia [she said she wanted me to take her to a place in Oregon where they euthanize people] and I got so sad I went into our freight elevator area and cried.  Sobbed.  Later in the day, left work... and went and saw Portishead, who were great.  But right before the show, I looked at my phone and saw immediately on Twitter that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/8056647043/&quot;&gt;Steve Jobs had died&lt;/a&gt; and I cried again.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am so pleased for my friends. They are wonderful people, they are wonderful together, and we should all be so lucky.  Today is a far happier day.</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=606</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=606#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 07:20:54 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=606</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>Big Changes Around Here</title>
<description>Now that I've gotten back in the swing with a new gig and have gotten in the habit of doing something productive with my life, that being productive has beget more productivity, though that hasn't yet extended to my yoga practice.  It has, however, gotten me into a bunch of new cool web stuff I've not done much with over the past few years, given me some new ideas, and so I finally gave this neglected site some much needed TLC and added some cool stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, the site is a hundred pixels slimmer and have hidden the overflow of &lt;a href=&quot;http://flickr.com/photos/evanrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;&gt;my Flickr photo stream&lt;/a&gt; and trimmed down some of the descriptions on the header links.  I also got rid of the contact page (which at one time contained a contact form that I got rid of long ago) and moved the functionality that displayed the ten most recent (though infrequent) blog posts to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://evanrose.com/archive&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Archive&quot;&gt;archive page&lt;/a&gt; which now contains the last ten posts by default, the ability to choose posts by month, or if passed a post ID, a permalink page.  Some work under the hood included a bunch of changes to the site's date and time functionality, as when I built this site almost ten years ago, I didn't understand PHP's date and time functionality very well so cleaned up a ton of crappy date/time crap, deleted old deprecated code, and did a lot of general refactoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new cool jam here though is &lt;a href=&quot;http://evanrose.com/&quot;&gt;the home page&lt;/a&gt; which has a bunch of new stuff.  I built a script that, when called by a &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cron&quot;&gt;cron job&lt;/a&gt; every hour, grabs my most recent 22 &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/evanrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Twitter&quot;&gt;Tweets&lt;/a&gt; (why 22 is the limit, I have no idea), my 15 most recent &lt;a href=&quot;http://evanrose.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt; image posts (which are 500 pixels wide, hence the site's new slimness), and the last ten evanrose.com blog entries (which are obviously way down at the bottom of the page as there aren't many recent ones), puts them all together, and then saves them in a separate file in reverse chronological order. This file is then included on the home page which, because it's just included and not requesting all this stuff every  time the page loads, the page loads much faster.  I know anyone who comes to this site probably already looks at my stuff elsewhere, but this was a fun project and I feel like this site hasn't gotten as much attention it's deserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next up: taking those tweets and Tumblr posts and putting them into my database, downloading the Tumblr photos to keep here for safekeeping, and having that same script update my RSS feed on a daily basis with a digest of the stuff I've put on the internet that day.  If you've made it this far, you are now an honorary nerd.  Welcome to the club.</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=605</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=605#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 14:16:19 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=605</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>The End of Summer</title>
<description>It isn't the end of summer, technically, but new things start on Memorial Day weekend and other new things start on Labor Day weekend.  Lots of things went on and here are some of them:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;weddings attended: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;states visited: 6.5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pools swam in: 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beaches visited: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visits to beaches in New York: 4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visits to pools in New York despite my saying I was going to ride my bike to one every day: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;times I actually rode my bike to the pool: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;golf lessons: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;new lows: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;trips to Boston: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;times someone tried to pick me up on the street: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;times they succeeded: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;friends in town: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sunsets watched: 2.5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;times fried okra was eaten: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;really, really unpleasant experiences: 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;dental surgeries: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;books read: 9&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;times key was left in motorbike's ignition: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;times that caused a huge problem: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;meals at Applebee's: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visits to Staten Island: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;friends who died: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;funerals attended: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;iPhones smashed: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;concerts attended: 2.5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;concerts missed: 1.5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;irons purchased: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;times on television: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;birthdays celebrated: 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New York documentaries finished: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;meals at the Chef's Table: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Diner en Blancs attended: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visits to the Cloisters: 0 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visits to Governors Island: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;days worked: 0&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jobs offered: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;jobs accepted: 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look out Fall, here we come!  I'm looking forward to a shorter list at the end of it.</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=604</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=604#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 06:07:01 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=604</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>New Things</title>
<description>A new year (just started on my 36th a fact that makes my mother impossibly young), &lt;a href=&quot;http://evanrose.tumblr.com/post/26641886639/happy-birthday-to-me-rolex-datejust-steel&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Tumblr&quot;&gt;a new watch&lt;/a&gt;, a new DJ mix (about which I've been talking forever), and a really amazing yoga and meditation practice.  The second half of 2012 is going very well and I like that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm not posting a ton here, but you can keep up with me on &lt;a href=&quot;http://facebook.com/evanrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Facebook&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/evanrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Twitter&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://evanrose.tumblr.com&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Tumblr&quot;&gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://flickr.com/evanrose&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;.  </description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=603</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=603#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 05:34:19 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=603</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>New Objectives</title>
<description>More joy&lt;br/&gt;
Less fear&lt;br/&gt;
Greater rate of fulfillment [a shorter time between wanting the &lt;b&gt;right thing&lt;/b&gt; and achieving it]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally: golf, private yoga instruction, daily bicycling and swimming and returning to paleo (minus the eggs and the bacon)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were some others though, that I can't remember, things I need to tape up on my mirror at home and read every time I look in it.  I need to keep having the kinds of conversations where ideas like these come up.  They're good for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS Happy spring, it was great to see all of you in Dallas, even under such sad circumstances, and I've made it home safe and sound.  Lots of love.</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=602</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=602#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 10:42:31 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=602</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>December 2011, Recapped</title>
<description>Finally, this is over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Met &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stephen_Sondheim&quot;&gt;Steven Sondheim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Went to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gowanuscanalconservancy.org/ee/index.php/gcc_news/gcc_news?id=97&quot;&gt;a crazy fundraiser for the Gowanus Canal&lt;/a&gt; and saw tons of people I hadn't in forever.  The night went downhill from there&lt;br/&gt;
Mom came into town&lt;br/&gt;
Went to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.christies.com/features/auctions/1211/elizabeth-taylor-collection/&quot;&gt;Elizabeth Taylor jewelry auction&lt;/a&gt; show at Christie's&lt;br/&gt;
Saw the new 9/11 memorial&lt;br/&gt;
Started Tristam Shandy, but couldn't get it going - put it down and started God Bless You Mr. Rosewater&lt;br/&gt;
Got super sick&lt;br/&gt;
Went to Los Angeles to visit Stephen, Maggie and Carolyn and had mad fun (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/sets/72157628540293559/&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;&gt;pics&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br/&gt;
Went to San Francisco/the Bay Area to see Brian, Justin &amp;amp; Mary, Avery  &amp;amp; Cortney and Peter  &amp;amp; Stacy and all their younguns (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/sets/72157628540293559/&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;&gt;pics&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br/&gt;
Saw a great Dieter Rams exhibition at SF MoMA and ate at In N' Out Burger &lt;br/&gt;
Went to Las Vegas to hang with my dad and stepmom and had mad fun (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/evanrose/sets/72157628540293559/&quot; title=&quot;Evan Rose Flickr&quot;&gt;pics&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br/&gt;
Made an unexpected pit-stop in Philadelphia&lt;br/&gt;
Went to the Cline's Christmas Eve pary and then had a fantastic Christmas dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;http://redroosterharlem.com/&quot;&gt;Red Rooster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Got hell of sick, again&lt;br/&gt;
Went to Boston&lt;br/&gt;
Rang in the new year seeing a great burlesque show at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dresslernyc.com/&quot;&gt;The Dressler&lt;/a&gt;</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=601</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=601#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 12:16:14 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=601</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>October 2011, Recapped</title>
<description>Went to all kinds of cool things in Portland; Beast, Sparrow, the Japanese and Rose gardens&lt;br/&gt;
Learned my one of my doctors had died&lt;br/&gt;
Learned Steve Jobs had died, for the second time that day, and saw Portishead (also may have noted that it'd been 25 years since the day I broke my leg)&lt;br/&gt;
Had a lovely evening at the Lamb's Club, Grand Central, and Pipa*&lt;br/&gt;
Saw the ballet Jewels, which was lovely&lt;br/&gt;
Saw Trans Am play Futureworld in its entirety after a great day&lt;br/&gt;
Kinda started going bananas*&lt;br/&gt;
Got an iPhone 4 to replace my ailing 3GS and soon after, dropped and smashed it, but ended up getting it fixed for free&lt;br/&gt;
Went to an opening which had a couple of Trevor Young's in it and a party at Romainian place&lt;br/&gt;
Had a Charlie Chaplin fest at Pink Pony&lt;br/&gt;
Went on a circle line boat tour around Manhattan which was hell of fun&lt;br/&gt;
Blew through a season of The Office&lt;br/&gt;
Finished Most Elligible Dallas, which sadly, ended before its prime&lt;br/&gt;
Saw Amon Tobin perform ISAM which was incredible&lt;br/&gt;
Went to a great birthday party at Cafeteria and Vepenios(?) and tons of peops came.&lt;br/&gt;
Went to Bayside (and played the drums), came back, went to a dinner party, watching football all day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news, this is the 600th post since I built the content management system on which this blog runs in 2002!

&lt;!--
With Erica, and I consider that to be our first date
Went on a sex binge and started really considering leaving B
--&gt;</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=600</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=600#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 07:23:20 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=600</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>April 2012</title>
<description>Gave up cheese for the month (which lasted all of five days when I made a loophole for Wing Day [and Mac n' Cheese day]), left Austin, finished Hunger Games, started some trashy Jack Reacher book (Worth Dying For), went to a super fun gallery opening and dance-after-party, saw The Hunger Games at Nighthawk, saw the &lt;a href=&quot;http://bldgblog.blogspot.com/2007/10/without-walls-interview-with-lebbeus.html&quot;&gt;Lebbeus Woods&lt;/a&gt; show and then went to the New York Auto Show, had a fun day in Harlem including going to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dnainfo.com/new-york/20120410/washington-heights-inwood/take-train-for-20-year-jazz-tradition-heights&quot;&gt;Jazz Salon&lt;/a&gt;, saw A Dangerous Method, had a sad dinner at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yelp.com/biz/upstate-new-york-2&quot;&gt;Upstate&lt;/a&gt;, went to &lt;a href=&quot;http://http://www.littlefieldnyc.com/event/103639/&quot;&gt;Krautwerk 1-8 Condensed: Kraftwerk Covered&lt;/a&gt; which was awesome, saw jazz at Uniqlo, started watching the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pbs.org/wnet/newyork/&quot;&gt;Ric Burns New York documentary&lt;/a&gt;, read Reamde by Neal Stevenson, met a crazy couple and had a bad end to a fun day, got laid off, saw &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bam.org/view.aspx?pid=3969&quot;&gt;Questlove show&lt;/a&gt; at BAM (with Deerhoof, Jeremy Ellis, Sasha Grey, Reggie Watts, and more), something bad happened, saw Do the Right Thing, Meloncholia, Salo, This Film is Not Yet Rated, and Antichrist, got scraped by a new periodontist, twice, had an extremely unfortunate encounter, something good happened and then had one of the best meals and best service I can recall at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yelp.com/biz/rye-brooklyn&quot;&gt;Rye&lt;/a&gt;, Zach and his brother Noah came into town, went to Jeramy's sparkle party (and not only ate some cheese, but had pizza for the second time in way more than six months), saw &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1758692/&quot;&gt;Like Crazy&lt;/a&gt; and got very, very sad, went on my first bike ride of the year.  A really up and down and crazy month.  </description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=599</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=599#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 06:51:07 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=599</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
<item>
<title>March 2012</title>
<description>Saw Moneyball, finished Breakfast at Tiffany's, went to LA for the day, first class (where I saw Dennis Leary and Paul Dano), and hung with Carolyn and Stephen, finally ate at Animal, ate at Isa, had an unfortunate encounter*, re-started and later finished Time, Sex and Power, finally caught up with How I Met Your Mother, Trevor came into town for the Armory Show (Pulse, Scope, Arts Not Fair, The Armory Show, etc.) and we had hell of fun, lost my passport, started Einstein's Dreams for the umpteenth time, fought with a cabbie, went to a dinner party at Brian's, finished A Christmas Story (after two months), got a new driver license, watched The Trip, saw Squarepusher, got &quot;The new iPad&quot;, Zach came into town, saw The Kid on the Bike, watched three hours of Louis CK, went to the launch of Beer Table's Table Beer at Blue Ribbon, which Daria attended, flew to Dallas in order to get to Kansas City to see Larkin but didn't make it, so flew back, finished Sex, Time and Power, read my friend Kirk's book &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Noncombatants-Twilight-Storm-Novellas-ebook/dp/B007KH02LI/&quot;&gt;Noncombatants&lt;/a&gt;, went to a Mad Men season premiere at The Paley Center, started To Die For (trash novels for men), went to Dallas (again), started The Hunger Games, met Indigo K., one of the world's cutest babies, saw the homies, ate the fried okra, went to Austin, saw the homies, and that's where the month ran out.

&lt;!-- saw Susan on the back of a bike in williamsburg, being ridden by a dude who was not the dude she was with when I encountered her online a year or so ago --&gt;</description>
<link>http://evanrose.com/?entry=597</link>
<comments>http://evanrose.com/?entry=597#comments</comments>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 12:39:31 -0700</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://evanrose.com/?entry=597</guid>
<category>Misc</category>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
